I have a super cool Aurora master which
ฉันมี ปรมาจารย์ออโรร่าที่ เด็ด สุด ๆ
is like this really neat light display
เป็นเช่นนี้การแสดงแสงที่ประณีตจริงๆ
that can go on your ceiling in your
ที่สามารถไปบน เพดานของคุณในของคุณ
bedroom or your kitchen okay your
ห้องนอนหรือห้องครัวของคุณโอเค
bathroom oh yeah let's see let's
ห้องน้ำโอ้ใช่แล้ว เรามาดูกันเถอะ
actually get into the box
ได้จริง เข้าไปในกล่อง
I'm doing it yeah all right so courts
ฉันทำ ถูกต้องแล้ว
what kind of course have we got this is
แน่นอนว่า เราได้รับสิ่งนี้
it yeah a USB device keep it on the
ใช่ อุปกรณ์ USB เก็บไว้ใน
camera for us USB so okay it's USB
กล้อง USB สำหรับเรา โอเคมันคือ USB
two-barrel that's interesting and then
สองกระบอกนั่น น่าสนใจแล้ว
this one here which is just like audio
อันนี้ตรงนี้ซึ่ง เหมือนกับเสียง
is that audio it is yeah because this
เป็นเสียงที่ใช่มันเป็นเพราะ
actually has a built-in speaker I am
จริงมีลำโพงในตัวผม
it's red it's something and this is I
มันเป็นสีแดงมันเป็นอะไรบางอย่างและนี่ คือฉัน
guess a how to how to turn on the light
คาดเดาวิธีการเปิด ไฟ
yeah okay oh this is the action here so
ใช่โอเค นี่คือการกระทำที่นี่ดังนั้น
this is the Aurora master 12 LED 8 mode
นี่ คือโหมด Aurora Master 12 LED 8
LED ocean wave projector so apparently
โปรเจคเตอร์มหาสมุทรคลื่น LED เห็นได้ชัดว่า
what I'm understanding here sash is that
สิ่งที่ฉัน เข้าใจนี่คือสายสะพาย
this is meant to project the ocean onto
สิ่งนี้มีไว้ เพื่อนำเสนอมหาสมุทร
any rights in a variety of colors so the
สิทธิใด ๆ ในความหลากหลายของสีเพื่อให้
red ocean or the blue ocean okay so you
ทะเลสีแดงหรือทะเลสีฟ้าเพื่อให้คุณไม่เป็นไร
can see that there's a spot here for
สามารถ เห็นว่ามีจุด ที่นี่สำหรับ
batteries you need a screwdriver for
แบตเตอรี่ที่ คุณต้อง ใช้ไขควง
that I will need a screwdriver okay
ว่าฉันจะ ต้อง ใช้ไขควงไม่เป็นไร
we've all and then I guess here is I
พวกเราทุกคน แล้วฉันเดาว่านี่คือฉัน
guess you can plug it in via USB right
เดาได้เลยว่าคุณสามารถเสียบมัน ผ่านทาง USB ได้ ทันที
cool
เย็น
I wonder if you could actually plug that
ฉันสงสัยว่า คุณสามารถเสียบมันได้หรือไม่
then into your laptop and it would
จากนั้น เข้าไปใน แล็ปท็อป ของคุณ และมันจะ
actually it would function would you
ที่จริงมันจะทำงานคุณจะ
have to plug in also this audio thing
ต้องเสียบยังสิ่งนี้เสียง
into your lap so I guess if you want to
บนตักของคุณดังนั้นฉันเดาว่าถ้า คุณต้องการ
use it as a speaker so if you wanted it
ใช้มันเป็นลำโพงดังนั้นถ้าคุณต้องการมัน
to be playing say nature sounds of
ที่ จะเล่นพูดเสียงของธรรมชาติ
Ontario Canada and right nature sounds
ออนแทรีโอแคนาดาและ เสียงของธรรมชาติที่ถูกต้อง
from our RSS feed Bingham then you could
จากฟีด RSS Bingham ของเรา คุณก็ทำได้
actually have the ocean sounds
จริง ๆ แล้ว มีเสียงของมหาสมุทร
at the same time right or music or
ในเวลาเดียวกัน หรือเพลงหรือ
whatever else it has an auto shutoff
สิ่งอื่น ก็มีการ ปิดเครื่อง อัตโนมัติ
after one hour so you can fall asleep to
หลังจากผ่านไปหนึ่งชั่วโมงคุณจะนอนหลับได้
this and then it won't be playing all
สิ่งนี้แล้วมันจะไม่เล่นทั้งหมด
day so over here you can't quite see it
วันนี้คุณไม่สามารถเห็นได้
because it's white on white but that's
เพราะมันขาวบน พื้นขาว แต่นั่นคือ
an on/off and then an up and a down
เปิด / ปิดและ จากนั้น ขึ้นและลง
volume button okay and it looks like
ปุ่มปรับระดับเสียงโอเคและดูเหมือน ว่า
that's kind of it pretty simple device
นั่นเป็น อุปกรณ์ที่ค่อนข้างเรียบง่าย
yeah I do
ใช่ฉันทำ
should we plug it in let's okay well
เราควรจะเสียบเข้าให้ของดีไม่เป็นไร
bring it back over here okay so this is
นำ กลับมาที่นี่ ไม่เป็นไรดังนั้นนี่คือ
a lot bigger than I was thinking it
ใหญ่กว่าที่ฉัน คิด ไว้มาก
looks you know from the pictures on
ดูคุณรู้ จากภาพใน
Amazon you'll think that it's like the
อเมซอนคุณจะคิดว่า มันเป็นเช่นนั้น
size of a coffee cup or something like
ขนาดของถ้วยกาแฟ หรืออะไรทำนองนั้น
that this is that's a honkin huge latte
ว่านี่คือ ลาเต้ อันยิ่งใหญ่
right there great so I'm thinking it
มีสิทธิที่ดีดังนั้นฉันคิดว่ามัน
would actually project pretty large onto
โครงการจริงจะสวยขนาดใหญ่บน
a ceiling if can I can I unwrap this can
เพดานถ้าฉันสามารถ ฉัน สามารถ แกะกล่องนี้ได้
you get the gonna get these off there
คุณ จะได้รับ สิ่งเหล่านี้ออกไปที่นั่น
perfect there we go there we go
สมบูรณ์แบบที่นั่นเรา ไปที่นั่นเรา ไป
and there you are just plug it into your
และคุณก็ แค่เสียบเข้ากับคุณ
laptop and see if it just works okay
แล็ปท็อปและ ดูว่ามันใช้ได้หรือ ไม่
okay so you said there's a power button
โอเคคุณบอกว่ามีปุ่มเปิดปิด
here yeah it's right in the middle yeah
ที่นี่ ใช่มันอยู่ ตรงกลางใช่
oh yeah okay we've got some light so I
โอ้ใช่โอเคเรามี แสงสว่าง บางอย่าง ดังนั้นฉัน
wonder can you cycle through yep so
สงสัยว่าคุณสามารถ วนผ่าน yep ได้ ไหม
that's red
นั่นคือสีแดง
okay Oh party lights party lights let's
โอเค ไฟ ปาร์ตี้ไฟปาร์ตี้กันเถอะ
do it no way can we turn the lights dim
ทำมันไม่มีทางที่เราสามารถเปิดไฟสลัว
the lights and we're gonna see how that
ไฟและเราจะดูกันว่า
looks okay so this is this is pretty
ดู โอเคดังนั้นนี่คือสิ่งนี้ สวย
neat I don't know if you guys I gotta
เกลี้ยงเกลาฉันไม่ทราบว่าคุณจะ ต้อง
hold this up but this is pretty bright
ถือมันไว้ แต่มันก็ค่อนข้างสดใส
mm-hmm that's just on the ceiling of our
mm-hmm ที่ อยู่บนเพดานของ เรา
studio here just the drop ceiling and
สตูดิโอที่นี่ เพียงแค่เพดานหล่น และ
then you obviously wouldn't sleep
เห็นได้ชัดว่า คุณ จะไม่นอน
through the party lights like there's
ผ่านแสงปาร์ตี้เช่นนั้น
others you'll see wow it's really dark
คนอื่น ๆ คุณจะเห็น ว้าวมัน มืด จริงๆ
in here right so you can have this okay
ตรงนี้คุณจะได้โอเค
like the maps of Hell so this would like
เหมือน แผนที่ นรก ดังนั้นนี่จะเป็นเช่นนั้น
some gentle whale music or something
เพลงปลาวาฬ อ่อนโยน หรือบางอย่าง
[Applause]
[เสียงปรบมือ]
well you can see my shadow that's
คุณสามารถเห็นเงาของฉันนั่น
awesome yeah also you can actually see
ใช่แล้ว คุณสามารถ เห็นจริง ๆ
this yeah but it's it there's like this
ใช่ แต่มันมีอย่างนี้
fluid motion to it and and some of the
การเคลื่อนไหวของของเหลวกับมันและบางส่วน ของ
reviews on Amazon have said that it's
ความคิดเห็นใน Amazon ได้กล่าวว่ามันเป็น
janky that it's clunky that the the
janky ว่ามันเป็น clunky ที่
animation is not smooth but look at that
แอนิเมชั่น ไม่ราบรื่น แต่ ดูที่
looks good to me
ดูดีกับผม
we can actually see that could we switch
เราสามารถ เห็นได้ ว่าเราสามารถ สลับได้
the mode again to see sure yeah look at
โหมดอีกครั้งเพื่อดูให้แน่ใจว่าใช่ดู
how smooth that looks oh that's not the
วิธีการที่เรียบที่มีลักษณะโอ้ที่ไม่
one yeah Rhett it's got this like really
หนึ่งใช่ Rhett มันได้เช่นนี้ จริง ๆ
I want to see like a natural ocean Wow
ฉันต้องการที่ จะเห็น เหมือนมหาสมุทรธรรมชาติ ว้าว
partay there you go
มีบางส่วนที่คุณไป
I think blue is that's the one that's
ฉันคิดว่าสีน้ำเงิน ก็คือสิ่งนั้น
cool I could fall asleep to that sure
เจ๋งฉัน นอนหลับได้อย่าง แน่นอน
okay so that's what it looks like folks
ตกลงนั่นคือสิ่งที่ดูเหมือน ว่าคน
definitely has a smooth look to it you
แน่นอนมีลักษณะเรียบ ไป คุณ
can see like and what I'm looking for is
สามารถเห็น ชอบและสิ่งที่ฉันกำลังมองหาคือ
is there any point within the animation
มีจุดใด ในภาพเคลื่อนไหว
of it where it seems to like click or
ของมันที่มันดูเหมือนจะ ชอบคลิกหรือ
jump and I'm not seeing that at all
กระโดด และฉันไม่เห็นเลย
now I'm gonna get my head down in here
ตอนนี้ผมจะได้รับหัวของฉันลงที่นี่
so you're gonna see my shadow I want to
ดังนั้นคุณจะเห็นเงาของ ฉันฉันต้องการ
hear because my microphone is on my face
ได้ยินเพราะไมโครโฟนของฉันอยู่ บนใบหน้าของฉัน
so I've got my face right up to this is
ดังนั้นฉันจึงได้ใบหน้าของฉัน จนถึงสิ่งนี้คือ
there any sound from it and I hear
มีเสียง จากมันและฉันได้ยิน
nothing Sasha mm-hmm there's no sound
ไม่มีอะไร Sasha mm-hmm ไม่มีเสียง
there's no like there's no annoying like
ไม่มี อะไรที่ไม่ น่ารำคาญ
clicking sound of a motor or anything
คลิกที่เสียงของมอเตอร์หรืออะไรก็ได้
like that
เช่น นั้น
and if I look in here let's see if I can
และถ้าฉันดูที่นี่เรามาดูว่า ฉันสามารถ
actually get you a view I don't see any
จริง รับมุมมอง ฉันไม่เห็นใด ๆ
movement right where is the movement
การเคลื่อนไหวที่ ถูกต้องในกรณีที่การ เคลื่อนไหว
actually taking place it must be the
จริง ๆ แล้ว มันจะต้องเป็น
little lights inside must be spinning
ไฟด้านในจะต้องหมุน
just a little bit I'm not seeing it
เพียงเล็กน้อยฉันไม่ เห็นมัน
there's no motion and yet the the roof
ไม่มีการเคลื่อนไหวและยัง เป็นหลังคา
is getting that like I'm gonna blind
เริ่มที่จะเหมือนฉันจะ ตาบอด
myself staring at it but there's got to
ฉัน จ้องมองที่มัน แต่ก็ต้องทำ
be so I see how it works there is a lens
ดังนั้นฉันเห็นว่ามันทำงานอย่างไร มีเลนส์
there's a little tiny lens that is
มีเลนส์เล็ก ๆ นั่นคือ
moving around over top
ย้ายไปรอบ ๆ ไปด้านบน
the LEDs that's really smart but there's
ไฟ LED ที่ ฉลาด จริงๆ แต่ก็มี
no sound from the motion there's no
ไม่มี เสียงจากการเคลื่อนไหวไม่มี
motor sound or anything like that but I
เสียงมอเตอร์หรืออะไรแบบ นั้น แต่ ฉัน
can see if I look and blind myself that
สามารถดูว่าฉันมอง และตาบอด ตัวเองว่า
it is in fact a lens you can see that
จริงๆแล้ว มันเป็น เลนส์ที่ คุณเห็นได้
Sasha it looks like a magnifying glass
Sasha ดูเหมือนว่าแว่นขยาย
just kind of very subtly moving over top
เพียงแค่เคลื่อนที่อย่างละเอียดมากไปด้านบน
of those LEDs right that's what causes
ของ ไฟ LED เหล่านั้นถูกต้องนั่นคือสาเหตุ
that animation this would be perfect
แอนิเมชัน นี้ จะสมบูรณ์แบบ
with anybody like a child that needs a
กับใครเหมือนเด็กที่ต้องการได้
nightlight like a transition from a
กลางคืนเหมือนการเปลี่ยนจาก
nightlight to a relaxation yes I like it
กลางคืนเพื่อ การ ผ่อนคลายใช่ฉันชอบมัน
a lot I think that's really neat huh and
มากฉันคิดว่ามันเป็นเรื่องที่ เรียบร้อย จริงๆ แล้ว
it's got a built-in speaker we didn't
มันมี ลำโพงในตัวที่ เราไม่ได้ทำ
test the speaker here because that's not
ทดสอบ ลำโพงที่นี่เพราะนั่นไม่ใช่
really something that I really care
สิ่ง ที่ฉันสนใจจริงๆ
about but at the same time like if I
เกี่ยวกับ แต่ใน เวลาเดียวกันเช่นถ้าฉัน
wanted to I could plug it into a an mp3
ต้องการ ฉันสามารถเสียบเป็น mp3
player or something like that to be
ผู้เล่นหรือสิ่งที่ต้องการที่จะเป็น
honest what I'd probably do is is not
ความซื่อสัตย์ในสิ่งที่ฉันอาจจะทำคือไม่ใช่
use the speaker with that because I
ใช้ลำโพงกับสิ่งนั้น เพราะฉัน
usually have my phone charging on my my
มักจะ มีการชาร์จโทรศัพท์ของฉันในของฉัน
little lamp beside my bed right so I'll
โคมไฟ เล็ก ๆ ข้างๆเตียงของฉันดังนั้น ฉันจะ
just plug something into my phone and
เพียงแค่เสียบบางสิ่งเข้ากับ โทรศัพท์ ของฉัน และ
have it playing from there cool yeah
มีมันเล่นจากที่นั่น ใช่ใช่
that's pretty neat so that is available
ค่อนข้าง เรียบร้อยเพื่อให้สามารถใช้ได้
at cat5 dot TV slash Aurora Aurora as
ที่ cat5 dot TV เฉือน Aurora Aurora เป็น
per the link in the description below
ต่อลิงก์ในคำอธิบายด้านล่าง
[Music]
[เพลง]
[Applause]
[เสียงปรบมือ]